Dillon J. Ellis

Creative Solutions to Complex Problems

CONTACT

(770) 561-0377

www.dillonzellis.com

Dillonzellis@gmail.com

Atlanta, GA

SKILLS

Analytical Thinking

Problem Solving

Team Leadership

Organization

Problem Solving

Management Skills & Flexible

Strong Communication

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Expertise in various computer languages focusing web design. Languages including: JavaScript, SQL, PHP, Sass, HTML5, CSS3.

Proficiency in Microsoft Office Word, PowerPoint, & Excel.

REFERENCES

Resia Mcfarland

RLM Affairs

(678) 617-1654 resialynn@gmail.com Direct Manager/Owner

Darlene Curry

Babycakes Cupcake Bakery

(770) 895-7427 v.curry@live.com Store Manager

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hard-working, motivated individual. Well versed in various computer languages focusing web development with a background in empirical research studies from design to analyzing data. Possesses a Bachelor of Science, impeccable written and verbal communication skills, and excellent interpersonal skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DZ Designs, Atlanta, GA

Owner, Design and Development 2019-Present

- Acquired clients.
- Conducted client meetings to determine client needs for development and budget.
- Design and deliver product.
- Set up maintenance packages including hosting, updates, changes, backups, and security.

RLM Affairs, Gainesville, GA

Assistant Event Organizer, Jan 2017-Present

- Tailored events according to the personal tastes and budgets of clients, managing and exceeding expectations.
- Maintained a portfolio of vendors/clients, serving as primary point of contact.

RLM Florist, Gainesville, GA

Assistant Manager/IT Assistant, Feb 2015-Present

- Updated and maintained store website.
- Address and resolve guest concerns, maintaining brand loyalty and increasing customer satisfaction ratings.
- Train staff to deliver outstanding customer service

EDUCATION

University of North Georgia, Dalonegha, GA

Bachelor of Science in Psychological Sciences, GPA 3.6/4.0, December 2017

University of North Georgia, Gainesville, GA

Associate of Arts in Psychology, GPA 3.7/4.0, May 2015

Relevant Coursework: Statistics, Research Methods, Web Programming, Software Engineering, Databases

Awards & Honors: Independent research in review of publication/Conference Presentations

Extracurricular Activities: Psychology Club President